Guide to the Pete Hamill Papers BCMS.0081
Brooklyn Collection
Pete Hamill Papers
1900-2020
1980-2019
Brooklyn Collection
BCMS.0081
19.1 Linear Feet in 17 record cartons, 1 document box, and 1 oversize box.
Materials documenting the career of journalist and author Pete Hamill. The bulk of the collection includes items from Hamill's post-newspaper career, focusing on his books, speeches, public appearances, freelance articles and screenwriting.
Arrangement
Series 1: Subject Files and Series 2: Speeches maintain original order and folder titles.
Series 3: Writing is divided into three sub-series by topic. Original folder titles have been maintained, with proceeding book titles added to folder titles by the archivist.
Folder titles marked with an asterisk (*) and all dates have been added by the archivist.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Fukiko Aoki Hamill, 2021 and 2022.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to researchers without restriction.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of materials documenting the career of journalist and author Pete Hamill. The bulk of the collection includes items from Hamill's post-newspaper career, focusing on his books, speeches, public appearances, freelance articles and screenwriting. Items dated pre-1985 are photocopies.
Subject Files represent Hamill's own record keeping system for various professional and personal items, which he kept in multiple A-Z file structures. Correspondence in this series is mostly in the form of printed emails to professional contacts, former classmates, family, friends and fans. Items concerning freelance work, public appearances, interviews, travel and awards are also included. Hamill collected his research, correspondence and promotional materials for several books in the Subject Files, including A. J. Liebling: The Sweet Science and Other Writings and A Time it Was: Bobby Kennedy in the Sixties in the Subject Files.
Speeches include handwritten speech notes, promotional items and correspondence regarding scheduling. Speech items also appear in the Subject Files. Scripts and treatments are original material and adaptations of previous work.
Books and Articles include manuscripts, research, press, correspondence and promotional materials for novels Snow in August, Forever, North River and Tabloid City; collection of short stories The Christmas Kid: And Other Brooklyn Stories; memoirs Downtown: My Manhattan and A Drinking Life; introduction to Vietnam: The Real War: A Photographic History by the Associated Press; biographies Why Sinatra Matters and Diego Rivera and an article tracing the life of Robert Henry Best. Also included are materials for an unpublished novel called Belfast Novel or Billy Dillon's Magic Leg, loosely based on the life of Hamill's father. Materials for other books and articles appear in the Subject Files. Writing by Others includes an early manuscript of Angela's Ashes and a handwritten note from author Frank McCourt.
Biographical
William Peter Hamill was born on June 24th 1935 in Park Slope, Brooklyn to parents Billy and Anne Hamill (née Devlin), immigrants from Belfast, North Ireland. Hamill attended P.S. 107 and Holy Name of Jesus elementary school, working as a delivery boy for the Brooklyn Daily Eagle to earn extra money. In 1949 Hamill was offered a scholarship to attend Regis High School in Manhattan. In 1951 he transferred to St. Agnes for a short time before dropping out for a job as a sheet metal worker at the Brooklyn Navy Yard. During this time, he moved out of his family's home and began taking night classes at the Cartoonists and Illustrators School (now the School of Visual Arts). In 1952, Hamill enlisted in the U.S. Navy, using money from his G.I. Bill to study painting at Mexico City College.
After returning to New York, he worked as a designer for the Greek magazine Atlantis, and soon opened his own studio. He also began writing letters to the editor of the New York Post, several of which were printed. In 1960, Post editor Jimmy Wechsler responded to one of Hamill's letters with a job offer, a three-month trial working the night desk. Hamill was hired, but a 1962 printers' union strike temporarily closed the paper, leaving Hamill to write freelance for several publications including the Saturday Evening Post. In February 1962 he married Ramona Negron, and their daughter Adriene was born later that year. In 1963, Hamill moved with his wife and daughter to Spain, where he worked as the European correspondent for the Saturday Evening Post, covering conflicts in Ireland and Lebanon. The couple's second daughter Deirdre was born in 1964.
In 1965 Hamill rejoined the New York Post and was sent to Vietnam to cover the war. In 1968 he joined the campaign trail of friend and democratic primary nominee Robert Kennedy. Hamill was standing a few feet from Kennedy when he was assassinated, and helped to subdue assassin Sirhan Sirhan. Later that year Hamill published his first novel, Killing for Christ. He worked as a columnist for the Post from 1969-1974, publishing a collection of his columns in Irrational Ravings (1971) and a second novel, The Gift (1973). Hamill was awarded a 1976 Grammy for his work writing the liner notes on Bob Dylan's album Blood on the Tracks. Hamill and Ramona Negron divorced in 1970.
From 1977-1979 Hamill worked as a columnist for the New York Daily News, as an editor for the Mexico City News in 1987 and as a columnist for Esquire from 1989-1991. He also contributed articles to New York Magazine, Rolling Stone, Playboy, and the Village Voice, bringing his work to a national audience. In 1987 he married journalist Fukikio Aoki. He continued to publish his own work, including Dirty Laundry (1978), Flesh and Blood (1977), The Deadly Piece (1979), The Invisible City: Short Stories (1980), Guns of Heaven (1984), Loving Women (1989) and Tokyo Sketches: Short Stories (1992).
In 1993 Hamill was named Editor of the New York Post, a position he held for five weeks. The following year his memoir, A Drinking Life, was published to positive reviews followed by a second collection of his columns called Piecework (1996.) In 1997 he was named Editor-in-Chief of the New York Daily News, which he resigned after eight months. In 1998 he published the bestselling Snow in August, followed by News is a Verb (1998) and biographies Why Sinatra Matters (1999) and Diego Rivera (1999).
In addition to books and articles Hamill was also a screenwriter, adapting stories from his novels and writing original content. Hamill briefly appears onscreen in several films and is credited as a writer on ten made for TV movies. He also gave lectures and participated in talks at numerous universities, libraries and organizations, speaking about his career and promoting projects. His ninth novel, Forever, was published in 2003, and in 2004 New York University named Hamill Distinguished Writer in Residence at the Arthur L. Carter Journalism Institute. Following the appointment he published his second memoir Downtown: My Manhattan, followed by novels North River (2007) and Tabloid City (2011).
Hamill's final full-length publication, a collection of short stories called The Christmas Kid: And Other Brooklyn Stories was released in 2012. He was the recipient of numerous awards including the Columbia Journalism Award for Lifetime Achievement, the Ernie Pyle Lifetime Achievement Award and the George Polk Career Award. Hamill died on August 5, 2020 following heart and kidney failure. He is interred at Green-Wood Cemetery. On June 24, 2021 7th Avenue between 11th and 12th Streets was renamed Pete Hamill Way, in honor of his childhood home at 378 Seventh Avenue.
Related Materials
Brooklyn Historical Society newspaper collection ARC.258
Catholic churches of Brooklyn publications and ephemera 1986.016
Female authors of Kings County list 1995.008
Jennie Child manuscript 1973.129
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
If digital surrogates exist, they should be used in place of the originals whenever possible.
Floppy discs are unavailable due to technical limitations.
Journalists -- New York (State) -- New York; Authors, American |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Manuscripts (document genre); Scripts (documents); Correspondence; Irish Americans |z New York (State) |z Kings County; Immigrants -- New York (State) -- Kings County; Manhattan (New York, N.Y.); Vietnam War, 1961-1975; Belfast (Northern Ireland); Speeches
- Series 1: Subject Files
  - Sub-series 1.1: A-Z
    - A, 2013-2019 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Abrams/Anniversary, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - AOL, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Addiction Intro, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Ali, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Alloy Article, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Amram, David, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Amtrak, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Art News Intro, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Art News Intro Revised, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Art News/Material, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Art News Intro/Notes, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Assistant, Possible, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - "At SEA", 2001 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Atlas, James, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Hamill/Avedon, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Auchincloss Prize, 2007-2010 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Autism, 2008-2015 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Autism School, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Awards, 1998-2014 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - B, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Boxing Writers Association of America*, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Baker, Ken/NYTBR, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Barcelona, 2017 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Baseball Kids Book, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Baseball Intro, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Belfast Culture Fest, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Berliner Piece, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Berman, Pavil, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Billy Dillon, circa 2013 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Bio, circa 2005 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Birthday 84, 2019 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Birthday, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Birthday/History, 2018 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Blurbs, 2003-2007 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Book Lists, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Book Proposals, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Book Reviews, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Book Signing, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Books for Kids, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Boxing, 2005-2017 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Breslin/Intvw, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Briscoe, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Brooklyn, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - May 12/Bklyn B.H., 2007 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Bklyn Book Fest, 2010-2014 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Bklyn Book Fest, 2007-2013 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Bklyn Book Fest, 2018 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Brooklyn Noir, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Bryant Park 2005 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Business- French Edition, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Hamill by Students, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - C, 2005-2012 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Callahan Book, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Camus Event 4/28/15, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Camus Panel, 2015 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Caniff/Terry, circa 2000 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Capeci Book, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Breslin, 2003-2007 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Casasola, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Cassidy's Fall, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Cavett Show, 2006-2018 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - CBS Morning Show, 2019 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - CBS Sunday Morning, 2018-2019 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Characters, 2004, 2007, 2017 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Chelsea, 2005, 2017 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Children, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Christmas Story, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Cigar Aficionado, 2001, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - City of Islands, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Class/Times, 1996-2004 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Column Materials, 1997-2003 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Commonwealth Club, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Cone Review, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Cosgrove, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Cooper Union, circa 2000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Courage, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Courage, 1986, 1998-2004 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Credit Suisse, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Cristo Rey, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - C.V., 2019 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Dad/Belfast Stuff, 19871994 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Daily News, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Delhi Noir, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Death Panel, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Desk, circa 2000 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Doctoron Review, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Dodgers, 1989, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Dodgers/Daily News, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Downtown Hamill, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Driver's License, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Duggan, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - E, 2008-2015 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Eddie Adams Intro, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Emails, 2014 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Europe Docs, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Exhibits, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - F, 2009-2018 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Falcons Book, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Fans, 2014-2016 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Farrell, James T., 2003 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Farrell/LOA, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Fat Brain, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Feifer/Playbill, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Fenian Ram, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Fenian Ram/Correspondence, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - FIU, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - The Fly (Ch. Bk.), circa 2000 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Folger Library, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Forward Intro, 1997-1998, 2004-2006 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Genealogy, 1911, 1935, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - G, 2006-2018 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Garden Intro, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Gelb Review, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - German Rights, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - The Gift, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - The Gift/Pb., 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Gigante, Vincent, 2003-2015 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Giraldi/Poet, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - GIH, 2009-2018 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - GIH 2016-17, 2016-2018 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - GIH Board Mtg. April 2013, 2012-2013 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - GIH/Breslin/ 12/7, 2009-2015 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - GIH/Caroline, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - GIH/Events Future, 2006-2008 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Gish Prize, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Gish Prize '08 '09, 1999, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - GQ Article, 1983, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - GQ/Column, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Gonzalez, Henry B., 2001 (Box 3, Folder 12-13)
    - H, 2009-2018 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Haberman/Mar 2, 2004, 2017 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Hachette, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Hamill Quotes, 2018 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Hard Case/Briscoe, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Hemingway, E., 2018 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Health, 2008, 2015 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Herald Trib/Oneskes, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Hideouts, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Horse, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Huffington Post, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Hunter, Evan, 1995-2003 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - I, 2009, 2018 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - ICM, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Ink, 2013, 2018 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Interviews, 2008, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Investigators Intro, 2001-2003 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Interviews 2018 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - I-Pad, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Ireland, 1999-2007 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Ireland/Belfast Contacts, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Ireland Contacts, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Ireland Trip 2004, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Irish, 2003-2012 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Irish AMS, 2016 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Irish Parade, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Irish Stuff, 2005-2006, 2015 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Ahern Intvw, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Boland/Kennedy Intvw, circa 1975 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - I Notes, circa 2000 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - O'Hagan, M., 2001 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Ireland House ('04), 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Ireland/Gourmet, 2007 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Ireland/Living, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Ireland/Outline, circa 2008 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Ireland/US Council 6/24, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - US Ireland Forum, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Ahern, Bertie- Photographs*, circa 2010 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Ireland/Irish, 2007-2016 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Italian Clips, 2002, 2015 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Japan/Yellow Hankie, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Japan Rights, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Javits Letters, 2005, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - JFK Jr., 1999 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Jogger, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Josephson, Barney, 1988, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - K, 2015-2018 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Kalish, Jon, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Weldon, Keys, 2012, 2016 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Kerrigan Street, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Kinstler, 2016 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Killing for Christ, 2017 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Knicks '17, 2017 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Kriegel/Vegas, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - L, 2003-2018 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Lars, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Lebanon '78, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Leonardo/Hamill Script, circa 2000 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Letters, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Levine, David, 2008-2014 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Library '15, 2015 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Library of America, 2008-2009 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - LOA Immigration, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Liebling Chronology, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Liebling/Columbia, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Liebling/LOA, 2006-2011 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Liebling Notes, 2008-2009 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Liebling Notes, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Liebling NYU 3/31, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Libraries, 2012-2016 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Liebling/Promo, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Liebling 2 Review, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Liebling/Uncollected, 1954-1964, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Liebling/Vol 2, 2004-2009 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Lion's Head, 2016-2019 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Hamill/Little, Brown, 2003-2016 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Living Landmarks/ 11/2, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Louis A 1/22/07, 2006-2007 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Loving Women, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Lucha Libre, 2018 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Lupa Velez, 1999, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - M, 1999-2017 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Manuscript, circa 2000 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Manbeck, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Mailer/Nation, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Mann-Hesse, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - McBain, Ed, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - MCNY 2006, 2002, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - MCNY/Tweed Oct 24, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - MCNY/History Book, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - The 400/MCNY, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Media Contacts, 2009-2010 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - MERC, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Mexico, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Mex. Consul, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Mexico City College, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Mexico Outline, circa 2000 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Mexico Trip, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Visa/Mexico, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Mexican Society (Philad.), 2006 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Maiami, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Monterrey, circa 2000 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Mob- History of the Mob Movie/TV, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Mob/Research Notes, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - The Mob- Part I, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Mob/Documentary, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Morning Joe, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Movie, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Moynihan Medal 2/5, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Moynihan, Pat, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Museo Brady, 2005, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - N, 2008-2016 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Nast, Thos., 2002 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Nachman, 2002, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Natl Book Awards, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Neimans, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Newberg, Esther, 2017 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Newberg, Esther/ICM, circa 1997 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - New Orleans, 2016-2018 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - NY Exposed, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - NY Exposed, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - New York Minute 9/9/99, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - N.Y. Notes, circa 2000 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - New York Post, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - NYAA, 2006-2009 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - NY Academy of Art, 2005-2008 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - NYAA, 2006-2008 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - NYAH, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - NY Times, 2004-2010 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - New York Times/Obits, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - New Yorker, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - NYU J-School, 2016-2018 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - N.Y. Writers Hall of Fame, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Newsweek Japan/NY, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - NOLA, 2016-2018 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Notes, circa 2007 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - NYPD, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - NYPL, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - O, 2002, 2014-2017 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Obits, 2015-2016 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Obits Panel, 2016 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Obits, 2011-2012 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Old Age, 2018-2019 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Orphan Trains, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Overseas Press Club, 1999, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - P-Q, 1997-2016 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Packer, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Padraic, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Paris St. Germain (Football Club), 2018 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Players Club, 2007-2016 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Pratt, 1997-2012 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Powers, Bill, circa 2004 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Publicity, 1994-2012 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Public Stuff, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Public Appearances, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Personal Appearances, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - PW/April, 2005-2007 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - R, 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Regis, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Regis, 2011-2016 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Regis, 2003-2005, 2016 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Regis 50th/June 14, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Regis '06, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Regis/Mar 9/06, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Regis/2007 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Regis/2008, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Regis 2009 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Regis 2010, 2010-2011 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Regis HS, 2010-2018 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Regis MS., 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Regis Preface, 2012-2013 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Regis Book, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Regis Diploma, 1949, 2009-2011 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Regis/Pizza, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Research/Tools, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - RFK, 2018 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - RFK 1968, 1968, 2018 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - RFK "A Time it Was", 2008 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - RFK Intro, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - RFK Promotion, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - RFK Layout, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Riggio, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Roberts, Sam/Intro, 2008-2009 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Roberts, Sam, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Robinson, Jackie, 1956, 2009, 2018 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Robinson, Jerry, 2009-2010 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Rosenthal, Abe, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Runyon Intro, 2005-2009 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - S, 2005-2012 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Saudis/Journalists, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Short Stories, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Silurians, 2006-2008 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Sinatra, 1980, 1999-2015 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Sinatra, 1998-2015 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Sinatra, Frank, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Sinatra 9/24, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Sinatra/Bernhart, Milt, 1997-2015 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Sinatra/Promotion, 1998-2015 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Sinatra/Spanish, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Sinatra/Spanish, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Soccer Novel, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Solway Book, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - St. Brigid's 6/15, 2006-2008 (Box 7, Folder 25)